Guide to the Ladyslipper, Inc. Records, 1965-2011 and undated RL.10140
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Financial Series, 1975-2007; 1
  - Vendor Files subseries, 1976-2007; 1.2
    - Alexis Kochan/Olesia Productions, 1994-2006; 1 folders (Box 40)
    - Alix Olson/Feed the Fire Production, 2001-2006; 1 folders (Box 40)
    - Angels of Venice, 1996-2000; 1 folders (Box 40)
    - Ani DiFranco pre 1997, 1992-1996; 1 folders (Box 40)
    - Ani DiFranco 2001-, 2000-2002; 1 folders (Box 40)
    - Ani DiFranco 1997-2000, 1996-2000; 1 folders (Box 40)
    - Ani DiFranco 2002, 2001-2006; 1 folders (Box 40)
    - Anne Lister/Hearth Fire, 1996-2003; 1 folders (Box 40)
    - Annette, 2005; 1 folders (Box 40)
    - Ann Sweeten, 2002-2003; 1 folders (Box 40)
    - Antigone Books, 2004; 1 folders (Box 40)
    - Aquarius International, 1996-2003; 1 folders (Box 40)
    - Astor Place Recordings, 1999-2000; 1 folders (Box 40)
    - Ars Femina, 1992-2004; 1 folders (Box 40)
    - Atlanta Feminist Women's Chorus, 1999-2003; 1 folders (Box 40)
    - Aubrey Records, Inc., 1991-2002; 1 folders (Box 40)
    - Balcorman Films, 1995-1997; 1 folders (Box 40)
    - Bari Productions, 1999-2006; 1 folders (Box 40)
    - The Bird Sisters, 1992-1999; 1 folders (Box 40)
    - Britta Alexandra, 2001-2003; 1 folders (Box 40)
    - Bison Tales/Lori Frazier, 1995-1998; 1 folders (Box 40)
    - Burnham Woods Records, 1998-2003; 1 folders (Box 40)
    - Cake Records, 1998-2003; 1 folders (Box 40)
    - Camp Pleiades, 1999; 1 folders (Box 40)
    - Circle of Soul, 2001`-2007; 1 folders (Box 40)
    - Common Bond, 1994-2007; 1 folders (Box 40)
    - Copper Wimmin, 1999-2003; 1 folders (Box 40)
    - Edie Carey, 2000-2004; 1 folders (Box 40)
    - Ellis Paul, 2002-2003; 1 folders (Box 40)
    - Evergreen Music Recording, 1996-2001; 1 folders (Box 40)
    - Fox Lorber, 1998-2003; 1 folders (Box 40)
    - Sweet Medicine Women's Center, 2005; 1 folders (Box 40)
    - Richard Dermer Management, 2002-2003; 1 folders (Box 40)
    - Gloria Kaufman, 1994-1996; 1 folders (Box 40)
    - Goddess Music, 1999-2001; 1 folders (Box 40)
    - Goldenrod, 1991-1999; 1 folders (Box 40)
    - Grace Records, 1999-2002; 1 folders (Box 40)
    - GRD-Invincible, 1990-2001; 1 folders (Box 40)
    - Grrr Records, 1 folders (Box 40)
    - Hal Leonard Publishing Corporation, 1993-2000; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Hacate, 1999-2000; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - The Heretics, 1991-1992; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Hidden Waters Sound Sanctuary, 1992-2004; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Hillsound Music, 1987-1992; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Public Media Home Video, 1989-1995; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Hot Productions, 1996-2002; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Justina and Joyce, 1992-2006; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Ignition Distribution/Jett Williams, 1996-1997; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Irene Ferrera, 1988-2006; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Interworld Music, 1992-2003; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Joanna Lynden, 1993-2007; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Janalea Hoffman/Rhythmic Medicine, 1991-2006; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - J's Records and Tapes, 1992-1995; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Jelsa Palao/Big Feet Productions, 1990; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Kathy Hogan, 1998-1999; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Mark Weigle, 1991-2003; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Kim Fisher, 1995; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - LadyFest South, 2002; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Lillian Allen, 1999-2002; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - October Rose Productions/Linda Allen, 1997-2006; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Little, 1993-1994; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Louise Kessel, 1995-2000; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Live Sound Prod., 1993; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Lynelle Tyler, 1998-2002; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - MACROmedia, 1994-1995; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Madeleine Baumann-Graves, 1995; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Western Publishing Company, 1992; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Mahatti Music, 2002-2004; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Maryem Hassan/Doula, 1997-2007; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Mary Marzo, 2000-2009; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Master your Mind, 1992-1995; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Indianapolis Men's Chorus, 1996-2001; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Mila Drumke, 1994-2002; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Mimi Fox, 1988-1992; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Miraj, 1996; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Miriam L. Danu, 1993-1996; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Moka Case, 1992-1995; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Molly O'Rourke, 1993-1994; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Montana Blake, 1990-1996; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Moondancer Productions, 1994-1997; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Moonforce Media, 1989-1995; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Mike Moran, 1996-2001; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Morrisette, 1995-1997; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Moss Music Group, 1990-1997; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Motel Records, 1996; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Moving Forward Music, 1992; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Ms. Ter Records, 1999-2005; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Musical Transformations, Inc., 1995-1997; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Music by Marcey, 1992-1995; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Music Sales Corporation, 1993-1997; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Musimedia, 1993-1997; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - My Sister Jane, 1991-1996; 1 folders (Box 41)
    - Nancy Day, 1984-2000; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Nancy Thompson, 1996-2000; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Natural Reaction, 1994-1997; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Northeastern Digital Recording, Inc., 1993-1995; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Nedra Johnson, 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Nervy Girl-Laura Wetzler, 1991-1995; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - New Age Retailer, 1995; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - New Alliance Records, 1994-1997; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - New Dimensions Radio, 1992-1997; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - New Moon Music, 1997; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Newport Classics, 1990-1996; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - New Weave Records, 1993-1996; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - New World Records, 1996-2001; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Nicki Scully, 1996; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Nicole Dubus & Susan Springfield, 1993-1996; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Nimbus Records, 1994-1997; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - North American Tapes, 1995; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Northword Press, 1994-1995; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - NYC Records, 1996-1998; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Octaves Beyond Silence, 1998-2005; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - On the Move, 1996; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Opalanga D. Pugh, 1986-1997; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Open Mind, 1993-1997; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Open Sky Music, 1987-1994; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Orbik Records, 1995-1998; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Original Music Inc., 1996-1997; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Jami Sieber, 1988-1995; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Oznaiim, 1992-1996; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Pacifica Program Service, 1992; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Pacific Cascade, 1977-1997; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Page Two, Inc., 1995-2006; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Pam Morgan, 1990-1995; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Paramount Publishing, 1994-1995; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Passport Music, 1995-1996; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Lisa Pawlak, 1991-1997; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Paws IV Publishing, 1994-1995; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - PC-SIG/Spectra Publishing, 1987-1992; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Peggy Seeger, 1999-2006; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Perfect Pitch, 2001; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Petronella, 1994-1998; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Phideaux, 1995-1997; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Phillips Enterprises, Inc., 1994-1995; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Pitney Bowes, 1996-1997; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Placenta Music, Inc., 1990-1992; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Pomegranate, 1988-1995; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Ponygirl Records, 1997-2001; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Pop Video, 1988-1995; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Portland Lesbian Choir, 1997-2004; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Potentials Unlimited, 1989-1990; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Ann Klein/P Prod Music, 1997-2003; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Present Moment, 1996; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - PLF Pride Center of NJ, 1994-1997; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Pridetime Travels, 1991-1995; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Primarily A Cappella, 1997-2004; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Prime CD's, 1995-1997; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Profile Productions, 1995-2000; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Purple Angel Records, 1991-1995; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Quaker Video, 1990-2002; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Qualiton Imports, 1997-1999; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Queens Group, Inc., 1989-1997; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Quest Publishing, 1997; 1 folders (Box 42)
    - Radhika Miller, 1984-1997; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Raindreaming Productions, 1992-1995; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Rainy Day Records, 1995-1996; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Ranch Romance, 1990-1995; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Rashani, 1987-1998; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Rashid Sales Company, 1984-2001; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Raven Recording, 1988-2000; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Toshi Reagon, 1994-1995; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Rediscover Music, 1995; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Reed Williams, 1995; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Regular Records, 1997; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Reiki Healing Institute, 1992-2001; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Reliable Office Supplies, 1996; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Resounding Records, 1993-1997; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Rewind, Inc., 1991-1995; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - RGB Records, 1994-1997; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Rhythmic Medicine, 1995; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - RMD Records, 1994-1998; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - The Righteous Mothers, 1995; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Cliff Townsend/RISCO, 1995; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Ritual Motion, 1995-1997; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - "Robin F" Flower and McLaren, 1991-1997; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Robin Tyler, 1985-1992; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Dutch East India Trading, 1995-1996; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Reach Out International Records, 1984-1993; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Room Of One's Own, 1996; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Roundabout Productions, 1992-1995; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Ruth King, 2002-2003; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Sampler, 1979-1995; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Sandy Rapp, 1986-1997; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Sapphire Percussion Ensemble, 1997; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Sappho's Isle, 1994; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Sara Hickman, 1995; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Sarah Stockwell, 1993-1994; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Tom Briggs/Saturn Disc, 1995; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Savell/Heartlight Records, 1986-2001; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Scream Sync Productions, 1993-2001; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - The Seal Press, 1991-1993; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Second Opinion, 1991-1994; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Select-o-hits, 1997; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Separations Unlimited, 1994; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Sequoia Records, 1998-2006; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Shanachie, 1998-2001; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Shefa Gold/B'Emet Records, 1996-2001; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - She Is, 1991-1995; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Sherri Hammons/Artemis Records, 1993-1997; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Directions Unlimited Productions/Sherri Sundly, 1992-2002; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Shirley Mae Springer Staten, 1996-2001; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Sibyl Publications, 1995-1996; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Sierra Records, 1993; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Silverlake Records, 1997; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Silver Lining, 1992-2001; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Simon and Schuster, 1995; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Singing Heart Productions, 1994-1996; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Sirius Records, 1992-1997; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Skin Talk/Carolyn Brandy, 1995-; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Sky Ladder Press, 1992-1995; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Skylark Productions, 1992-1997; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Small Kindnesses, 1992-1996; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Smithsonian Institution Press, 1993-1996; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Songs of Change, 1991-1993; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Songtalk Publishing, 1987-1995; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Sonia Johnson/Wildfire Books, 1988-1993; 1 folders (Box 43)
    - Sons and Lovers, 1995-1996; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Soundings of the Planet, 1987-2001; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Sound Marketing, 1995-2001; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Sources of Hope/Positive Voices, 1996-2001; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Soundstation Distribution, 1999-2001; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Spobs Music Inc., 2000-2003; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Square Deal Record Company, 1994; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Sri Chinmoy Bhajan Singers, 1991-1995; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - SST Records, 1993; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Squire's Own Music, 1993-1995; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Steve Lynn, 1995-1998; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - St. Martin's Press, 1994-1996; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Straight Arrow Productions, 1991-1993; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Streeter Productions, 1996-2002; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Sue Witty, 1995-2001; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Sugo Music & Design, 1995-1996; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Sunny McHale Skyedancer, 1992-1994; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Sunray Tapes & Literature, 1991-1995; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Susan Elizabeth Hale, 1989-2001; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Susan Maule, 1994-; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Susan Osborn, 2000-2003; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Susan Strauss, 1990-1996; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Suzanne McIntosh, 1993-1996; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Suzanne Sterling, 2001-2002; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Suzi Katz, 1992-1995; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Sweet Honey in the Rock, 2000-2005; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Sweet William Music, 1996-2001; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Tallapoosa Music, 1987-1992; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Tape Specialty, 1990-1992; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Ted Fox, 1993-1994; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Teresa Doyle, 1996-2001; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Terra Bella, 1988-1996; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Terrakia Records/Wishing Chair, 1996; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Terry Garthwaite, 1991-1997; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Te Whanau Productions, 1989-1991; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Tiana Marquez/Sol Invectus, 1997-2002; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Tiye Giraud, 1994-1995; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Tiik, 1993-1996; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Timeless Productions, 2000-2001; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Timeless Books, 1989-1991; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Time Line Productions, 1994-1996; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Tim Kerr Records, 1993-1995; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Tinder Records, 1997-2001; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Titanic Records, 1988-1997; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Tofa'Ah, 1997-2001; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Tom Yore, 1997; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Toronto Consort, 1995-2001; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Touchwood Records, 1997; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Transisters/Pink Rock Management, 1996-1998; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Triam Music/Jallen Rix, 1995; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Triloka Records, 1992-1997; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Trip Records, Inc., 1994-1996; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Tower Group International, Inc., 1995; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Turquoise Records, 1988-1992; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Twiggs Company, 2000-2002; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - UFD Publishing Co., 1993-1994; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Underwear Music, 1992-1995; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Upstate Media, 1989-1997; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Ursa Minor, 1995; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Planetary Publications, 1990-1995; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Video Data Bank, 1996-2001; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Vicki Pratt Keating, 1994-1997; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Vicki Richards/Third Stream Music, 1990-1993; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Video Marketing Group, 1994-1996; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Wahaba Records, 1991-1992; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Watchfire Records/Susan Herrick, 1994-2004; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Waterbug Records, 1994-1997; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Waterlily Distribution Corporation, 1989-1992; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Hilda Wenner, 1991-1994; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - White Sandkastle Productions, 1992-1997; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - White Wind Productions/Elizabeth Rhoades, 1996-2001; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Wildlife Productions/Melissa Michaels, 1997; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Wild Sanctuary, 1992-1994; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - William Morrow, 1990-1995; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Willow Tree, 1989-1997; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Wimmin on the Edge, 1991-1995; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - The Wimps/Vance Lehmkuh, 1991-1993; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - W.I.S.E., 1985-1995; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Wolf Records, 1990-1997; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Women, Women, and Song, 1988-1990; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Womontyme, 1986-1997; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Womyn's Music Video, 1 folders (Box 44)
    - War Resisters League, 1997; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - B'Kol Ishah/Yael Fischman, 1995-2001; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Yagottawanna, 1993-1997; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Yasmeen, 1991-1993; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Yeproc Records, 1998; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Yesyoumay! Music, 1993-1998; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Yoland Martinez, 1994-1995; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Zango, 2004; 1 folders (Box 44)
    - Jennifer Berezan/Edge of Wonder, 1989-1997; 1 folders (Box 45)
    - Halcyon Records-Norman McPartland, 1977-1998; 1 folders (Box 45)
    - Annual Returns, 1982-1995; 1 folders (Box 45)
    - Claudia Queen/Womonsounds, 1986-1995; 1 folders (Box 45)
    - Heartlight House, 1986-1995; 1 folders (Box 45)
    - Julia Haines, 1988-1995; 1 folders (Box 45)
    - Mary Retorts, 1986-1996; 1 folders (Box 45)
    - Beth York, 1985-2001; 1 folders (Box 45)
    - Marie Rhines, 1996-1998; 1 folders (Box 45)
    - Mother of Pearl, 1985-1994; 1 folders (Box 45)
    - Beverly Botsford, 1994-2003; 1 folders (Box 45)
    - Tiye Giraud, 1991-1996; 1 folders (Box 45)
    - Tribe of Spirit, 1994-1997; 1 folders (Box 45)
    - Susan Herrick/Watchfire Records, 1989-2004; 1 folders (Box 45)
    - Jami Sieber, 1995-2000; 1 folders (Box 45)
    - Sound Currents, 1983-2001; 1 folders (Box 45)
    - Empty Closet Entertainment, 1995-2005; 1 folders (Box 45)
    - Girls in the Nose, 1990-2001; 1 folders (Box 45)
    - Affirmations, 1989-2002; 1 folders (Box 45)
    - Barbara Borden, 1989-2003; 1 folders (Box 45)
    - Edwina Lee Tyler/Percussion Piquant, 1989-1999; 1 folders (Box 45)
    - Rachel Bagly/Outta the Box, 1990-1996; 1 folders (Box 45)
    - Sue Fink, 1985-1996; 1 folders (Box 45)
    - Two Nice Girls, 1992-1995; 1 folders (Box 45)
    - Refine/Disappear Records, 1990-1998; 1 folders (Box 45)
    - miscellaneous correspondences and order forms, 1998-2002; 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Letter and Report Responding to BPs 5-5-1982 Letter, 1982-1984; 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Email re: Alliance Records, 1998; 1 folders (Box 46)
    - A/P Procedural Information, 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Financial Materials 1996-1998, 1996-2001; 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Valley Media bankruptcy, 2001; 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Vendor Returns, 1999-2001; 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Unentered Problem Invoices, 1998-2005; 1 folders (Box 46)
    - No Shipping Vendors, 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Miscellaneous documents about pricing, 1996-2002; 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Spring 1997 ads, 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Wholesale advertising--Summer 1997, 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Ad Summaries, 1995-1998; 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Catalog Ad Sales Fall 1998, 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Fall 1997 Retail Ads, 1997-1998; 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Fall 1996 Ads, 1996-1997; 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Spring 1995 Ads, 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Fall 1995 Ads, 1995-1996; 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Checks, CMs, and ads Fall 1994, 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Topp twins, 1996; 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Listen Line, 1995; 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Listen Line Holiday, 1995; 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Fall Retail 2000, 2000-2001; 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Ad Action File, 2001; 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Summer Fall Wholesale 2000, 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Spring 2000 Retail, 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Retail Holiday 2000, 2000-2002; 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Summer/Fall Wholesale, 1999; 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Spring 1999 Retail, 1999-2000; 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Fall 1999 Retail, 1999-2001; 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Retail Holiday Catalog 1999, 1999-2000; 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Winter 99 Wholesale, 1999-2000; 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Winter '98 Wholesale, 1998-1999; 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Spring 98 Ads, 1998; 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Summer/Fall Whole Advertising 1998, 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Fall 1998 Retail, 1998-1999; 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Winter Wholesale, 1997-1999; 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Spring 2002 Wholesale Catalog, 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Miscellaneous Retail, 1999-2001; 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Fall Retail 2001 Catalog, 2001-2002; 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Spring Wholesale 2001, 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Holiday 2001 ads, 2000-2002; 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Spring 2001, 1 folders (Box 46)
    - Ad Thank You and (Original) Invoice & Dark Letterhead, 1 folders (Box 46)
    - US Postal Service, 2003-2005; 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Fall 2001 Postal Receipts, 2001-2002; 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Spring/Summer 2001 Catalog Mailings, 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Fall 2000 Mailings, 2000-2001; 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Spring Mailings 2000, 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Fall 1999, Wholesale mailing, 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Fall Mailings 1995 Post Office receipts, 1999-2000; 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Spring 1999 Mailings, 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Fall 1998 Mailings, 1 folders (Box 47)
    - 1998 Mailings, 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Fall 1997 Mailings, 1 folders (Box 47)
    - 10/98 Postal Rates, 1998; 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Fall 1996 Mailings, 1996-1998; 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Spring 1996 Mailings, 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Spring 1995 Ret Mailing Codes, etc., 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Fall 1995 Mailings, 1995-1996; 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Spring 1995 Catalog Mailings, 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Fall 1993 Catalog Quotes, 1994-1995; 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Fall 1992 Quotes/Spring 1993 Quotes, 1992-1995; 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Fall 1994 Mailings, 1994-1995; 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Spring 1994 Catalog Mailings, 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Spring 1993 Mailings Post Office Receipts, 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Company Permit, 1993-1999; 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Post Office Regulations/News, 1993-1995; 1 folders (Box 47)
    - P.O. Applications For Additional Mailing Office, 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Continuing List Search, 1993-1994; 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Spring 1993 Catalog Mailing, 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Fall 1992 Mailings, 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Fall 1993 Mailings, 1 folders (Box 47)
    - 1992 M.L. Analysis, 1993; 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Fall 1992 Catalog Mailings, 1992-1993; 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Spring 1992 M.L. Codes, 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Greensboro Permit, 1996; 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Village Mailing Screw-Up Sept-Oct 1992, 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Fall 1990 Catalog Codes & Analysis, 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Fall 1990 Catalog-List Plans, 1991; 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Postal Barcoding, 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Post Office Receipts--Fall 1991, 1991-1992; 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Fall 1991 Mailing Lists, 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Spring 1991 Mailing, 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Catalogs Mailings-USPS-Spring 1992, 1991-1992; 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Catalog Quotes, 1992; 1 folders (Box 47)
    - 1991-New Mailing List Ideas, 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Spring 1991 Postal Stuff, 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Fall 1990 Post Office Receipts, 1990-1991; 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Fall 1990 Catalog Mailings--Problems! And Pissed Off Catalog Recipients, 1991; 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Backroads-ML Trade?, 1990; 1 folders (Box 47)
    - 4AD Envy CD, 1995; 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Abacus, 1994-1995; 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Antigone Associates, 1992; 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Astraea, 1994-1995; 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Bookwoman Books, 1994; 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Campfest, 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Children's Catalog Lists, 1 folders (Box 47)
    - CMG Information Services, 1994; 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Coalition for Peace & Justice, 1 folders (Box 47)
    - The Company of Women, 1989-1991; 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Direct Communications Inc., 1993-1994; 1 folders (Box 47)
    - Daedalus, 1997-1999; 1 folders (Box 47)